[LAUGH ING]
(Raj:)My turn.
(Penny(entering):)Okay, first of all, what you call a gap
was nearly three feet wide.
(Penny(entering):)- I slipped and skinned my knee.
- Are you okay?
[BUZZING]
(Penny:)The door to the stairwell
of the other building was locked.
(Penny:)I had to go down the fire escape,
which ends on the third floor...
(Penny:)...forcing me to crawl through the window
of a lovely Armenian family...
(Penny:)...who insisted I stay for lunch.
(Leonard:)That doesn't sound too bad.
(Penny:)It was eight courses of lamb.
And they tried to fix me up with their son.
(Penny:)- Sorry.
- Not done.
By the time I got to work,
they'd given my shift away.
(Penny:)Yeah, that's right.
I've lost an entire day's pay thanks to this.
(Sheldon:)- This...
- Time machine.
(Leonard:)The lights flash and the dish spins.
Wanna try?
(Sheldon:)No.
I don't wanna try it.
My God, you are grown men.
How can you waste your lives
with these stupid toys...
(Penny:)...and costumes and comic books,
and now that?
(Raj:)- That...
- Again, time machine.